Guide to the Richard Maass Collection of Westchester and New York State 1645-1995, (Bulk: 1645-1910) MSS.055
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Westchester
  - Subseries A: Letters and Documents
    - creator: Clinton, Henry, Sir, 1738?-1795. place: Headquarters, Philipsburgh, Jun 18, 1779; 055-002-A-0613; 5 pages (Box 7, Folder 103)
      To Lord George Germain. Reports the capture of Stony Point and Fort Lafayette.
    - creator: Clinton, Henry, Sir, 1738?-1795. place: Mamaroneck, Jul 10, 1779; 055-002-A-0619; 3 pages (Box 7, Folder 104)
      Approval of death sentence for a deserter.
    - creator: Weiss, Jacob, 1750-1839. place: [Fishkill], Sep 7, 1779; 055-002-A-0623; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 105)
      physical description: full sheet folded, fragments missing.; d.s.
      Order for supplies from John Fisher.
    - creator: Howe, Robert, 1732-1786. place: Pines Bridge, Oct 12, 1779; 055-002-A-0624; 3 pages (Box 7, Folder 106)
      Requests assistance from an unknown recipient for Commodore Bourne.
    - creator: Tallmadge, Benjamin, 1754- 1835. place: Canaan, Oct 21, 1779; 055-002-A-0628; 3 pages (Box 7, Folder 107)
      To Colonel Jermemiah Wadsworth.
    - creator: Pell, Philip. place: [New York], Oct 25, 1779; 055-002-A-0632; 2 pages (Box 7, Folder 108)
      dimensions: 22cm x 15cm
      Certification of an account as Member of the Assembly.
    - creator: Mumford, David. place: Cortlandt's Manor, Nov 5, 1779; 055-002-A-0635; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - creator: Biddle, Clement, 1740-1814. place: New Windsor, New York, Nov 6, 1779; 055-002-A-0636; 4 pages (Box 7, Folder 110)
      To Nathanael Greene.
    - creator: Unknown author place: s.l., 1780; 055-002-A-0641 (Box 7, Folder 111)
      physical description: bound volume with paper boards and leather spine; orderly book
      extent: [156] pages
      Orderly Book for unidentified unit.
    - creator: Bigelow, Timothy, 1739-1790. place: Highland, Jan 27, 1780; 055-002-A-0642; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 112)
      dimensions: 20cm x 21cm
      To Captain Greenleaf.
    - creator: Badlam, Ezra. place: White Plains, Jun 4, 1780; 055-002-A-0643; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 113)
      Printed furlough form made out for Joseph Thomas and signed by Ezra Badlam.
    - creator: Fogg, Jeremiah. place: West Point, Jun 27, 1780; 055-002-A-0644; 4 pages (Box 7, Folder 114)
      dimensions: 34cm x 22cm
      To an unknown correspondent regarding recent military actions.
    - creator: Steuben, Friedrich Wilhelm Ludolf Gerhard Augustin, Baron von, 1730-1794. place: Fishkill, Jul 29, 1780; 055-002-A-0649; 4 pages (Box 7, Folder 115)
      dimensions: 37cm x 23cm
      To Pierre Duponceau.
    - creator: Rose, John. place: Hartford, Sep 28, 1780; 055-002-A-0654; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 116)
      physical description: fragment; d.s
      dimensions: 19cm x 17cm
      Receipt for pay, partially printed. Signed by John Rose
    - creator: Cove, Joshua. place: Hartford, Sep 28, 1781; 055-002-A-0655; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 116)
      Receipt for pay, partially printed. Signed by Joshua Cove.
    - creator: Troup, Robert, 1757-1832. place: Fishkill, Jan 1, 1781; 055-002-A-0656; 3 pages (Box 7, Folder 117)
      To Hugh Hughes.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: Dobbs Ferry, Jul 13, 1781; 055-002-A-0660; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 118)
      physical description: full sheet folded; a. d.s.
      Orders for an attack on New York City.
    - creator: Parsons, Samuel Holden, 1737-1789. place: Dobbs Ferry, Aug 1, 1781; 055-002-A-0661; 2 pages (Box 7, Folder 119)
      physical description: half sheet with additional partial sheet with address; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 20cm x 30cm
    - creator: Stewart, Charles, 1729-1800. place: Dobbs Ferry, Aug 8, 1781; 055-002-A-0664; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 120)
      dimensions: 38cm x 23cm
      To Thomas Jones.
    - creator: Heath, William,1737-1814. place: Dobbs Ferry, Aug 9, 1781; 055-002-A-0668; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 121)
      physical description: fragment mounted in paper frame; l. s.
      dimensions: 15cm x 18cm
      To Samuel B. Webb.
    - creator: Shute, William. place: Dobbs Ferry, Aug 19, 1781; 055-002-A-0669; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 122)
      To his commanding officer regarding supply difficulties.
    - creator: Van Schaick, Goose, 1736-1789. place: King's Ferry, Aug 22, 1781; 055-002-A-0670; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 123)
      dimensions: 37cm x 25cm
      To Polly [Van Schaick].
    - creator: Roberts, Stephen. place: Peekskill Heights, Sep 25, 1781; 055-002-A-0673; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 124)
      Bill for Roberts' service in Connecticut militia.'
    - creator: Roberts, Stephen. place: Peekskill Heights, Sep 25, 1781; 055-002-A-0674; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 124)
      dimensions: 21cm x 15cm
      Certificate for Roberts's service in the regiment of Col. Samuel B. Webb. Signed by Edward Bulkley.
    - creator: Sewall, H. place: Highlands near West Point, Jan 29, 1782; 055-002-A-0679; 4 pages (Box 8, Folder 125)
      physical description: half sheet folded; a.l.s
      dimensions. 37cm x 23cm
      To his brother, [Jotham] Sewall
    - creator: Sewall, H. place: Robinson's House, Mar 18, 1882; 055-002-A-0684; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 125)
      dimensions: 35cm x 23cm
    - creator: Sewall, H. place: Head quarters, Continental Village, Sep 26, 1781; 055-002-A-0675; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 125)
      dimensions: 33cm x 20cm
      To his brother [Jotham] Sewall
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: Newburgh, May 10, 1782; 055-002-A-0687; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 126)
      Letter dictated to Colonel Dayton dictated by Washington in the hand of David Humphreys.
    - creator: Dayton, Elias B. place: Elizabeth Town, May 15, 1782; 055-002-A-0690; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 127)
      To [Henry Van Schaack]
    - creator: Heath, William, 1737-1814. place: Highlands, May 24, 1782; 055-002-A-0691; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 128)
      dimensions: 23cm x 35cm
      To Major Clift.
    - creator: Dispostion of the Five Companies on the frontiers of Ulster and Orange Counties place: Marbletown, Jun 15, 1782; 055-002-A-0694; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 129)
      physical description: full sheet folded.; a. d.
      Orders for the arrangement of troops, establishment of posts and distribution of supplies around Ulster and Orange Counties.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: Headquarters, Jun 24, 1782; 055-002-A-0698; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 130)
      physical description: full sheet folded, missing portion of second leaf; l. s.
      To Governor Livingston.
    - creator: Loring, Joshua. place: New York, Jul 10, 1782; 055-002-A-0702; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 131)
      Request for debts owed by American prisoners to be exchanged at Dobbs Ferry or Bergen.
    - creator: Olney, Jeremiah, 1749-1812. place: Dobbs Ferry, Aug 29, 1782; 055-002-A-0703; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 132)
      physical description: half sheet; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 31cm x 19cm
      British soldiers exchanged at Dobbs Ferry.
    - creator: Baily, John place: Kakiatt, Sep 14, 1782; 055-002-A-0704; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      physical description: fragment; a.d.s.
      Receipt for corn, oats and hay.
    - creator: Baily, John place: Kakiatt, Sep 14, 1782; 055-002-A-0709; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      Receipt for corn, oats, buck wheat and hay.
    - creator: Helm, William place: Kingston, Sep 14, 1782; 055-002-A-0708; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - creator: Baily, John place: Camp Near Pines Bridge, Sep 30, 1782; 055-002-A-0712; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      dimensions: 22cm x 20cm
      Receipt for flour, pork, mutton and rum.
    - creator: Baily, John place: Camp Near Pines Bridge, Sep 30, 1782; 055-002-A-0713; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      dimensions: 22cm x 18cm
      Receipt for corn, rye, oats and hay.
    - creator: Helm, William place: Camp Near Pines Bridge, Sep 30, 1782; 055-002-A-0710; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      dimensions: 22cm x 10cm
      Receipt for hay.
    - creator: Helm, William place: Camp Near Pines Bridge, Sep 30, 1782; 055-002-A-0711; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      Receipt for rye and oats.
    - creator: Helm, William place: Camp [Pine's Bridge], Sep 30, 1782; 055-002-A-0714; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      Receipt for flour, pork and rum.
    - creator: Baily, John place: Kingston, Sep 7, 1782; 055-002-A-0706; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - creator: Helm, William place: Kingston, Sep 7, 1782; 055-002-A-0707; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      dimensions: 22cm x 12cm
      Receipt for corn and hay.
    - creator: Helm, William place: Kingston, Sep 7, 1782; 055-002-A-0706; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 133)
      dimensions: 21cm x 13cm
    - creator: Baker, Asa place: [Hartford], [1783]; 055-002-A-0717; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 134)
      physical description: fragment; a.l.s
      dimensions: 23cm x 18cm
      Request for back wages signed by Asa Baker and S. F. Swift.
    - creator: Benjamin, John place: Hartford, Jan 2, 1784; 055-002-A-0716; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 134)
      physical description: fragment, partially printed; d.s.
      Receipt for back wages paid to Asa Baker.
    - creator: Grosvenor, Thomas place: Verplanck's Point, Sep 9, 1782; 055-002-A-0715; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 134)
      physical description: half sheet; a.d.s.
      Request for wages due for Connecticut regiments, signed by Thomas Grovesnor.
    - creator: Villemanzy, Jacques-Pierre Orillard, comte de. place: Crompond, Sep 18, 1782; 055-002-A-0718; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 135)
      To Colonel Wadsworth.
    - creator: Heath, William,1737-1814. place: Verplanck's Point, Sep 19, 1782; 055-002-A-0721; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 136)
      To Hon. M. Marbois.
    - creator: Wadsworth, Jeremiah, 1743-1804. place: Peekskill, Sep 22, 1782; 055-002-A-0722; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 137)
      dimensions: 21cm x 25cm
      To Aaron Burr.
    - creator: Starrs, Ichabod place: Camp Near Pines Bridge, Oct 1, 1782; 055-002-A-0723; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 138)
      physical description: half sheet; a.d.s
      Records goods received and delivered on the march from Baltimore to Pecks Kill.
    - creator: Quinby, Josiah. place: New York, Dec 23, 1782; 055-002-A-0724; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 139)
      Authorization of trade of goods to Quinby. Signed by David Mathews.
    - creator: Sheldon, Elisha, 1740-1805. place: [Connecticut], Jan 1, 1783; 055-002-A-0725; 4 pages (Box 8, Folder 140)
      Pay order for his regiment for service between the years 1780 and 1781.
    - creator: Humphreys, David, 1752-1818. place: Headquarters [Newburgh], Jan 2, 1783; 055-002-A-0730; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 141)
      To Colonel William S. Smith.
    - creator: Clinton, George, 1739-1812. place: Poughkeepsie, May 20, 1783; 055-002-A-0731; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 142)
      physical description: half sheet, multiple repairs.; a.l.s.
      To George Washington. Plans for surrender of Westchester by British.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: [Newburgh], Jun 14, 1783; 055-002-A-0732; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 143)
      physical description: half 1heet; l. s.
      To Ralph Izard.
    - creator: Pell, Philip. place: Westchester County, Oct 9, 1784; 055-002-A-0733; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 144)
      Claim against forfeited estate of George Cornwell.
    - creator: Pickering, Timothy, 1745-1829. place: Philadelphia, Oct 22, 1784; 055-002-A-0734; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 145)
      To Udney Hay.
    - creator: Yeomans, Eleazar. place: Cortlandt, Jul 13, 1790; 055-002-A-0737; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 146)
      dimensions: 18cm x 31cm
      Grants power of attorney to Philip Van Cortlandt.
    - creator: Smith, Isaac. place: Westchester, May 18, 1792; 055-002-A-0738; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 147)
      dimensions: 37cm x 32cm
      Coroner's inquisition regarding the death of Isaac Smith. Signed by 19 Westchester residents.
    - creator: Britt, James., August 21, 1792; 055-002-A-0742; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - creator: Britt, James., [1792]; 055-002-A-0745 (Box 8, Folder 148)
      physical description: fragment; a.d.
      extent: [1 page]
      Record of Britt's service in the army in unidentified hand.
    - creator: Britt, James., October 13, 1792; 055-002-A-0746; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 148)
      dimensions: 20cm x 14cm
      Sells rights to Van Cortlandt for back pay.
    - creator: Clinton, George, 1739-1812. place: New York, Jun 24, 1793; 055-002-A-0747; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 149)
      To Gerard Bancker. Payment of reward for capture of John Ryer who murdered a Westchester County deputy sheriff.
    - creator: Munro, Peter Jay. place: [White Plains], Apr 10, 1800; 055-002-A-0748; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 150)
      physical description: half sheet folded, multiple repairs, hole.; a.l.s.
      To William Barker.
    - creator: Jay, John, 1745-1829. place: Bedford, Oct 12, 1801; 055-002-A-0752; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 151)
      dimensions: 41cm x 29cm
      To William Livingston.
    - creator: Ludlow, William W. place: New York, Sep 1, 1803; 055-002-A-0753; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 152)
      To Charles Ludlow.
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Augustus. place: [Yonkers], Mar 1, 1808; 055-002-A-0754; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 153)
      physical description: fragment, portion torn off.; a. d.s.
      Slave document signed by Van Cortlandt.
    - creator: Radcliff, Jacob, 1764-1844. place: New York, May 4, 1811; 055-002-A-0755; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 154)
      physical description: wove paper; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 40cm x 24cm
      To Andrew DeWitt.
    - creator: Richardson, Samuel M. place: Pelham, Jun 23, 1812; 055-002-A-0759; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 155)
      physical description: laid paper fragment; a.d.s.
      dimensions: 16cm x 22cm
      New York National Guard is federalized for the War of 1812.
    - creator: Jay, John, 1745-1829. place: Bedford, Mar 28, 1820; 055-002-A-0760; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 156)
      physical description: wove paper; a. n. s.
      dimensions: 39cm x 25cm
      To Dr. Samuel F. Jarvis, together with retained draft of Jarvis letter to Jay.
    - creator: Jarvis, Samuel F. place: [New York], 1820; 055-002-A-3095; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 156)
      physical description: wove paper; a. l. s.
      dimensions: 10cm x 17cm
      Draft of letter to John Jay on the death of his daughter.
    - creator: Morris, James. place: Morrisania, Jan 27, 1825; 055-002-A-0761; 4 pages (Box 8, Folder 157)
      physical description: full sheet, leaves detached; a. d.s.
      Copy of will for James Morris.
    - creator: Lee, Robert P. place: Somers Town, Feb 4, 1831; 055-002-A-0766; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 158)
      physical description: wove paper; a.d.s.
      Rental agreement between Robert P. Lee and Jacob Van Tassell.
    - creator: Jay, William, 1789-1858. place: Bedford, Nov 7, 1833; 055-002-A-0769; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 159)
      To Professor Elizur Wright, Jr. Formation of a national anti-slavery society.
    - creator: Austin, John. place: Yorktown, Feb 12, 1838; 055-002-A-0772; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 160)
      physical description: wove paper; d.s.
      Memorandum of an agreement made between John Austin and Robert P. Lee regarding Lee's farm.
    - creator: Irving, Washington, 1783-1859. place: Sunnyside, Oct 1, 1846; 055-002-A-0775; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 161)
      To William Bailey Long.
    - creator: Brown, Benjamin M. place: Westchester County, Jun 9, 1847; 055-002-A-0776; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 162)
      physical description: wove paper; a. d.s.
      Official certification of election results in Westchester County.
    - creator: Andrews, W. R. place: Sing Sing, Oct 7, 1852; 055-002-A-0777; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 163)
      To Francis Toomes.
    - creator: Carpenter, Richard, 1784-1859. place: Scarsdale, Jan 4, 1856; 055-002-A-0778; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 164)
      physical description: ruled blue wove paper; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 40cm x 26cm
      To Richard Mott.
    - creator: Irving, Washington, 1783-1859. place: Sunnyside, Jul 15, 1859; 055-002-A-0781; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 165)
      dimensions: 25cm x 21cm
      To Alfred L. Barbour.
    - creator: Mother place: Dobbs Ferry, Mar 5, 1863; 055-002-A-0784; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 166)
      physical description: ruled wove paper; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 20cm x 19cm
      To my beloved Jack, signed your loving Mother.
  - Subseries B: Oversize Materials
    Series II: Subseries B contains oversize material, mainly consisting of deeds and other records of land grants inWestchester. These are housed in a flat box, with the exception of one item which is kept in the map case.
    - creator: Smeeman, Herman place: New York, Oct 22, 1664; 055-002-B-1890; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 1)
      physical description: full sheet, multiple folds and some repairs; d.s.
      dimensions: 36cm x 47cm
      Sale of land by Herman Smeeman to Samuell Edsall.
    - creator: Leisler, Jacob place: Westchester, May 31, 1690; 055-002-B-1891; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 2)
      dimensions: 49cm x 36cm
      Conveyance of a tract of land (New Rochelle) within Pelham Manor by John Pell to Jacob Leisler for settlement by the Huguenots, subsequent transactions relating to New Rochelle of various dates.
    - creator: Heathcote, Caleb. place: [New York], Jun 25, 1702; 055-002-B-1892; 1 pages (Folder 1)
      physical description: vellum; d.s.
      dimensions: ??
      Indenture of Westchester county land originally purchased by Heathcote, divided among eleven men, including Cornelius De Peyster, Robert Walter, and Robert Lurting.
    - creator: Hallock, John. place: s.l., Apr 19, 1776; 055-002-B-1893; 2 pages (Box 9, Folder 4)
      dimensions: 38cm x 35cm
      Sale of land in Courtland manor to Lewis and Edmund Palmer.
    - creator: Greene, Nathanael, 1742-1786. place: [Verplanck's Point], Aug 4,1780; 055-002-B-1896; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 5)
      dimensions: 45cm x 35cm
      To Clement Biddle. Describes George Washington's crossing of the Hudson.
- Series III: Mayors and Governors Autographs
  Series III contains correspondence and other documents signed by mayors of New York City and Governors of New York State (and New Jersey). It is arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Letters and Documents
    Series III: Subseries A contains materials which represent the broadest range of dates in the collection. It begins with a document signed by the first Van Cortlandt, Oloff Stevenson, a burgomaster of New Amsterdam, and concludes with a check signed by William Gaynor, an early twentieth century mayor of New York City. The selection of governors is equally diverse, and includes two documents signed by the notorious Lord Cornbury (Edward Hyde) as well as the extremely rare autograph of George Clarke.
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Oloff Stevenson. place: [New Amsterdam], 1655; 055-003-A-1897; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 1)
      physical description: fragment; d. s.
      dimensions: 19cm x 9cm
      Financial document. Signed by Van Cortlandt.
    - creator: Bayard, Nicholas, 1644-1707. place: [New Amsterdam], Mar 29, 1674; 055-003-A-1898; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 2)
      physical description: full sheet folded; a. d. s.
      dimensions: 31cm x 41cm
      'New Orange in America.'
    - creator: Andros, Edmund, Sir, 1637-1714. place: New York, Jun 11, 1679; 055-003-A-1899; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 3)
      physical description: half sheet; d. s.
      Docketed: warrant of Gov. Andros commanding the seizure of the sloop of Richard Botts. Signed by Andros and Matthias Nicolls.
    - creator: Wyllys, Samuel. place: New York, May 11, 1682; 055-003-A-1900; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 4)
      physical description: half sheet with paper seal; a. d. s.
      1801 or 1802 copy of deed noting change of name of Hop Ground plantation to Bedford.
    - creator: Limerick, Thomas Dongan, Earl of, 1634-1715. place: Fort James, Apr 24, 1686; 055-003-A-1901; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 5)
      physical description: full sheet folded; d. s.
      Docketed: Proclamation prohibiting trafficking with Indians. Signed by Dongan.
    - creator: Bayard, Nicholas, 1644-1707. place: New York, Sep 10, 1687; 055-003-A-1902; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 6)
      physical description: half sheet, partially printed.; d. s.
      Naturalization paper for Balthazar Bayard.
    - creator: Leisler, Jacob, d.1691. place: Fort William, Jul 31, 1690; 055-003-A-1903; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 7)
      physical description: full sheet folded, badly damaged; a. l. s.
      To Ensigne John Hedman regarding the seizure of Albany by insurrectionist forces.
    - creator: De Peyster, Abraham, d.1768?. place: New York, Jun 12, 1693; 055-003-A-1904; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 8)
      physical description: full sheet, folded and silked.; d. s.
      dimensions: 48cm x 38cm
      Deed to a house sold by Jacobus Van Cortlandt to Anthony Lepinar. Signed by De Peyster as mayor, Van Cortlandt, witnessed by Rip Van Dam and Cornelius Jacobs. Original item moved to Oversize 7/23/2004 by Mike Kelly, see Series IIIB Box 1 Folder 2.5, but a transcription is available in 8A.
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Stephanus, 1643-1700. place: New York, Jun 2, 1696; 055-003-A-1905; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 9)
      physical description: half sheet; a. l. s.
      To Kiliaen Van Rensselaer.
    - creator: Bellomont, Richard Coote, Earl of, 1636-1701. place: Boston, Nov 29, 1699; 055-003-A-1906; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 10)
      To Mr. Blaithwait
    - creator: Lodowick, Charles. place: London, May 20, 1700; 055-003-A-1907; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 11)
      dimensions: 19cm x 15cm
      Receipt of payment for merchandise. Signed by Lodowick (i.e. Lodwyck) Docketed on the reverse.
    - creator: Hyde, Edward, Earl of Clarendon, 1661-1723. place: New York, Dec 18, 1707; 055-003-A-1908; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Docketed: Administration of his father's estate granted to John Bugby. Signed by Cornbury.
    - creator: Hyde, Edward, Earl of Clarendon, 1661-1723. place: New York, Mar 3, 1707/8; 055-003-A-1909; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 13)
      physical description: full sheet, trimmed; d. s.
      Grants administration of the estate of Francis Rombouts to Roger Brett. Signed by Cornbury.
    - creator: Lister, Charles. place: London Tower, Jan 5, 1709; 055-003-A-1910; 3 pages (Box 10, Folder 14)
      physical description: two full sheets, quired; a. l. s.
      To Col. Robert Hunter The letter relates to the preparations undertaken by Hunter for his assumption of the Governorship of New York.
    - creator: De Peyster, Abraham, d.1768? place: New York, May 1709; 055-003-A-1914; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 15)
      physical description: partially printed documents, repaired conjugate leaves?; d. s.
      Two indented bills, no. 3360 (for ten shillings) and no. 3320 (for five shillings), Signed by De Peyster, R. Walter and R. Lurting.
    - creator: Ingoldsby, Richard, d.1759. place: Perth Amboy, Jun 10, 1709; 055-003-A-1917; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Grants administrator's rights to Thomas Hayward for the estate of Joseph Woodroofe. Signed by Hayward and Ingoldsby.
    - creator: Ingoldsby, Richard, d.1759. place: [New York], Dec 24, 1709; 055-003-A-1920; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Authorizes Thomas Byerly to purchase lands in New Jersey from its Indian owners. Signed by Ingoldsby.
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Jacobus. place: New York, Dec 12, 1710; 055-003-A-1923; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 18)
      physical description: fragment, mounted in paper frame; l. s.
      Legal document relating to the inability of several witnesses to appear for a defendant because they must go to sea. Signed by Van Cortlandt.
    - creator: Hunter, Robert, 1666-1734. place: Albany, Oct 10, 1711; 055-003-A-1924; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 19)
      physical description: fragment, silked; d. s.
      dimensions: 21cm x 19cm